

Cristian M. Dacer

cristiandacer29@gmail.com | github.com/cristiandacer29

Portfolio: cristiandacer29.github.io/CristianM.Dacer

0948-8627-159

Bulawan Sr., Lupi, Camarines Sur

Profile

A Bachelor of Science in Information Technology graduate from Central Bicol State University of Agriculture Sipocot Campus <u>CBSUA</u> batch 2019. I have almost 5 years of experience in a manufacturing company, working as a production controller that focuses on handling operators and employees in the production area. Also, we handle company product data to create reports like product forecasts and product operations. My strength is in digital art like logo design and graphic design. I have knowledge in web development, but as of now, due to lack of experience in actual work in web development, I like to focus on the front end.

Skills

- Computer literacy
- Creativity
- Technical support
- Basic Database Management (MySQL)
- Programming (HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP)

- Framework (BootStrap)
- Knowledge in Microsoft Office
- Knowledge in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
- Basic 3D using Blender application
- Knowledge in web development

Experience

Production Controller

Nito Seiki Manufacturing Corporation (2019 - 2024)

Seminar art work shop

Central Bicol State University of Agriculture (2018)

On the job training Information and Communication Technology Department

Central Bicol State University of Agriculture main Campus (2018 - 2019)

On the job training University Library

Central Bicol State University of Agriculture main Campus (2017 - 2018)

Education background

• Tertiary education

Center Bicol State University of Agriculture

Sipocot Camarines Sur - 2019

Secondary education

St. Peter Baptist College Foundation

Poblacion Lupi Camarines Sur - 2015

Primary education

Bulawan Sr. Elementary School

Bulawan Sr. Lupi Camarines Sur – 2010

Character Reference

Rodelyn V. Baet

OIC Production Control Department

Contact No.: 0956-1392-037

Mark Gil Diaz

Supervisor Power Press Department

Contact No.: 0968-6582-722